和
and
我们正在直播
we are live
欢迎大家来到
welcome everybody to
我想你们中的大多数人都看到了一些熟悉的面孔。
this amazing panel i think most of you all see some
熟悉的面孔
familiar faces here
我是你们今天的共同主持人
what i'm what you're co host today
我叫Tracy，你可以在Twitter上关注我。
my name is tracy you can follow me on twitter
我是Lady Lee的首席执行官，是一家名为Des dot labs的咨询公司。
at lady lee i'm the ceo of a consultancy called des dot labs
今天我有一个
and today i have a
他是一个软件开发人员，在这个点
who is a software developer here at this dot
我们非常非常兴奋地在今天的会议结束时
and we are so so excited to close out
我们很高兴能在今天的会议上结束这个精彩的小组讨论
the day with this amazing panel
所以感谢大家
so thanks all for
谢谢大家一整天的支持
hanging in there all day
你知道，也许我们可以快速地转一转
and you know maybe we can just go around really quickly
并做快速的名字介绍
and do quick name introductions
对于那些你不知道的
for those of you don't know
这就是我们的团队，我从伊万开始说起
this is the beat team and i'll start with evan
你好，我是Evan，我是
hello i'm evan and i'm
作者和团队领导的节拍
the author and team lead for beat
你好，我是新加坡人
hello i singapore
好的
okay
你好
hello
我是好请讲
i'm好请讲
来自Beat和View Gs团队
from the beat and view gs team
所以我在view gs组织工作
so i work for the view gs organization
你可能在github上认识我，叫苏打茶。
full time and you may know me on github as soda tea
我的工作地点在中国
i'm based in china
好的
okay
我是Ethany傻瓜，我是一个Wid编码成员，也是
and it's ethany fool here and i'm a wid coding member and also
我创建了一些
i create a few
的插件和工具，如维塔斯和滑块。
wid pluggings and tools like vitas and slider
是的，谢谢Patak
and yeah thanks patak
是的
yeah
我是Matthias，我也被称为Patak。
i'm matthias i also known as patak and
我也是这个团队的一员
i'm also part of the team
我在Starblitz工作，在那里我得到了像
and i work at starblitz where i get to spend like
我在Starblitz工作，最近在那里花了很多时间。
full time in bit lately
你好，约翰，你好
hello john hello
我是Tier，我是A V和Sabel的成员，也是Corresident Astro的成员。
i'm tier i'm t member of a v and sabel and corresident astro i'm
是的，我们也可以开放源代码
yeah we can open source as well
和
and
下一个和谐Shini
next harmony shini
是的，你好，我是克里斯托弗，又名
yeah hello i'm christopher aka
又名Chinigami
as known as chinigami
我也是V团队的一员
and i'm also a member of the v team and
当我有时间的时候总是在工作，在我的空闲时间里
always working when i have time in my free time
在小麦和耶
at wheat and yeah
你拿着东西
and you take stuff
哦，非常感谢你的介绍
oh thank you so much for the introductions
我们可以直接进入小组讨论了
and we can get right into the panel
好的，第一个问题是
okay so the first question is
会议对你来说是怎样的？
how was the conference for you
让我们继续，并从以下方面开始
let's go ahead and start with
情绪化 是情绪化
emotional was it emotional
令人惊讶 是的
surprising yeah
说实话，相当相当惊讶
quite quite surprising to be honest
我还记得我们第一次观看时的咳嗽声。
i kind of remember when we had the first view cough right
那是当面的，这个是虚拟的，但还是
that was in person this one's virtual but still
当他第一次
when that he has first
他第一次来的时候，跟我说了这个想法。
came and flowed the idea with me saying okay
我们想做一个V字形的咳嗽，我很怀疑，我当时想
we want to do a v cough i was quite skeptical i was like
你确定吗？
are you sure like
也许我们没有足够的人感兴趣
maybe we don't have enough people that's interested
但是
but
然后当他们开始
then when they start
真正开始工作的时候
actually started working on it
我看到越来越多的这些框架作者加入了
i see more and more of these framework authors getting on board
越来越多的框架作者加入到会谈中来，实际上在整个过程中，他们都在为之努力。
with talks and actually in the whole process leading up to it
马蒂亚斯是那种
mathias was kind of
给了我一些会谈的预告，你知道吗？
giving me spoilers of the talks you know
我越来越兴奋了，因为
i get more and more excited about it because
这其实很有趣，因为你知道当你
it's actually interesting because you know when you are
我们没有积极跟踪
we are not actively keeping track of
每个人在生态系统中都在做什么
what everyone's doing in the ecosystem
但现在同时每个人都在
but now at the same time everyone's
同时向你展示他们一直在做的所有事情
showing you all the things they've been working on at
同时
the same time
它给你带来了更大的
it gives you a much more
影响，你知道
impact you know
你会感觉到你创造的东西的影响，而且
you feel the impact of the thing you created and
看到所有这些
it's truly amazing to see all these
人在上面建造东西
people building stuff on top of the
是的
yes
yeah
任何其他评论 任何其他情感想法
any other comments any other emotional thoughts
来自Zay
from zay
没有，就像Evan说的那样
no yeah like evan said
这真的很有趣，很多这些曼陀罗
it has been really interesting that a lot of these mantanas
选择
choose
Vitcomf是他们做这个宣布的地方
vitcomf to be their place where they do this announcement
就像我们今天看到的那样
eh like we we saw today
伊恩从一本故事书中
ian from a storybook
说，在故事书的第七点O
saying that in the storybook seven point o
将会有这样的情况
there is going to be like
网络包不再需要了
the web pack was not going to be needed anymore
所以只有当你在Vitap中时才会有Vit。
so it's going to be vit only if you are in a vitap
所以这是个重大的消息
so like that's huge announcement
我们看到了，他们知道与Vit一起工作
we saw like they know working with vit
或
or
Lucas来自Rodap
lucas from rodap
特别是选择这种饮食方式来发布Rodap 3
choose this diet in particular to release rodap three
这对我们来说是很重要的
that is like enormous for us
就像我们现在需要开始在rodap 4上工作一样
like that we need to start working on rodap 4 now
但正如七号所说的那样，有很多事情
but as seven said like there there is like a lot of
今天发生的事情
things happening today
我们需要几周的时间来解读
it will take us like weeks to unpack
所有发生的事情，就在
everything that happens just
就像在过去的12个小时里
like in the in the past twelve hours
听起来有很多工作要做
a lot more work it sounds like
这当然是一种祝福
which is a blessing of course
对开放商来说是福也是祸
a blessing and a curse for opensores
嗯
well
你谈到了一些大的展览，但还有谁对这些展览有意见？
mts you kind of talked about a few of the big
种类的展示，但还有人对以下方面有意见吗？
kind of showcases but anyone else has comments on
任何一种像你感到兴奋的事情，当它
any kind of like things you're excited about when it
展示会或
comes to the showcase or
任何其他你觉得有趣的公告
any other announcements that you found interesting
是的，所以
yeah so
我在想，目前大约
i'm thinking currently about
一年半前
one and a half year ago
甚至你也对那个团队大喊大叫
even you made that team shout out
为寻找一个团队的节拍和
for looking for a team for beat and
是的
yeah
i
是的，我举起了我的手，我真的真的很高兴能加入这个生态系统。
raised my hand for that and i'm really really happy to be
在这个生态系统中，等等，现在
in this ecosystem now and so on and now
认为有一个会议
think that there's a conference
带来了所有这些框架维持我们和来自世界各地的
bringing all of this framework maintain us and from every
世界各地的人在一起
side of the world together
工作 是的，我们在一些培训中谈到
to work yeah we talked
在一些培训中谈到
in some trainings about
在过去
in the past
他们的框架是，但现在它更像是
their framework was but now it's more like
所有的框架都在一起了
all frameworks coming together
捆绑和杂草和
bundles and weed and
很高兴看到大家都在一起了
it's so nice to see that everyone is coming together
是的，这让我非常高兴
yeah that makes me really happy
还有
有什么意见吗？
any comments beyond any comments
是的
yeah
我想我必须要
i think i have to
给予材料一个巨大的支持，因为
give a huge shotout to materials because
我认为他是这个世界上唯一的人
i think he's the only person in this
在这整个前线和世界中
in this whole front and world to
掌握了海滩生态系统的全貌
get the whole picture of the beach ecosystem
这是我第一次看到这么多的
it's the first time that i've seen so many
包我们的团队在一周内
packages our teams around the week to
一起出现，并且
show up together and
我很高兴看到这个公告
i'm very excited to see the announcement
在我的时间里，所以它是在昨天晚上，卷起维持卢卡斯
in my time so it's last night that the roll up maintain lucas
那
that
实际上，从技术上讲，他并不属于GT生态系统的一部分
he actually technically he's not part of the gt ecosystem
因为他是一个通用的
because he's a universal
工具的前端，但他选择了
front end of tool but he choose to
用这个舞台来宣布
use this stage to announce that the
抟土机是开放的
roll up is open
为
for
rasta
改写，我想这对我来说是非常兴奋的。
rewriting and i think that's very excited for me
是的，我很兴奋，在Rula树是一个相当大的消息
yeah i'm quite excited in rula tree is quite a big news
我认为Steplets也在尝试
and i think steplets as well trying
这么多的功能，只是一个小小的谈话
so many features out and just one small talk
我迫不及待地想使用它
i can't wait to use it
而且我认为
and i think
我错过了很多会议，因为我必须要睡觉
i missed quite a bit of the conference because i have to sleep
但我肯定会在下半场赶上他们的。
but i'm definitely catching them in a second half
这真的很好
it's really good
是的，我必须承认，我还没有完成所有我的
yeah i have to confess that i haven't finished all my
我不得不承认，我还没有看完我所有的演讲，因为像顶部的内容是很疯狂的。
other talks since like top hours of content is crazy
是的，由于绑在一起的圆顶，我正要离开，我刚刚醒来。
and yeah due to the tying dome i was leaving and i just wake up
试图赶上会谈，所以我之前没有完成。
and trying to catch up the talks so i didn't finish before
在我们进入这个小组之前
before we go into this panel
但我想说的是，我对整个生态系统印象非常深刻。
but yeah i'd like to say that i'm really impressive about
我想说的是，我真的对整个生态系统印象深刻，这些创新的灵感来自于社区内部的合作。
the whole ecosystem the innovations created inspired by bits of
社区内部的合作，提出了很多想法
the collaboration inside of the community that come up with
这么多的想法和
so many ideas and to
像
like
涉及我们的日常工作流程或开发人员的经验，以
involve our daily workflows or developer experience to
所以是的，我真的对我们的社区印象深刻。
push that much forward so yeah i'm really
我对我们的社区印象深刻
impressed about the community we had
我对我们的社区留下了深刻的印象，因为我们的节奏和错误的节奏，是的
for the beat and the wrong beat yeah
好的
well
我只是
and i will just
试着完成所有的谈话
try to finish all the talks
今天晚些时候
later today
是的
yeah
我也一样，其实我错过了不少。
same for me i actually missed quite a few of them
所以我也在努力追赶
so i'm trying to catch up as well
但这是我的想法
but that was the idea
它需要像这样工作，因为现在你喜欢
it needs to work like that because now you like
整个亚洲和欧洲都有机会看到这些作品了
all of asia and europe also has opportunity to see them all
这很好
that's good
有一件事我很喜欢
and one thing i like
聊天就像Shini说的那样，一直是这样的
the chat as shini was saying like it has been like this
就像它已经有11个小时的
like it has been like eleven hours of
像内容
like content
一个持续的内容，来自
a constant content from
就像很多社区一样，当
like a lot of communities when
这很有趣，因为像
it was interesting because like
我不知道，就像在实星
i don't know like in the solid star
与Ryan的谈话
talk with ryan
整个固体社区都来到了Withland
the whole solid community came to withland
他们在那里谈话，然后像
and they were talking there and then like the
在 "快狗 "里也是这样
in the quick dog the same was there
或在下一个股票中，如
or in the next stock like
景观社区也在那里，而且
the view community was there and
就像在一个特定的渠道，它是像
like in one particular channel it was like
疯狂的速度
crazy how fast
文字是去
the text was going
有多少人在那里互动
of how many people were interacting there
是的，从这个角度来说，有很多事情要做。
yeah branching off of that there's a lot going on
在一个会议期间
during a conference
团队是如何合作的
how does the team work together
我的意思是，由于时区和一切，你如何
i mean with the time zones and everything how do you
团队是如何一起工作的？
how does the team get to work together
是的，所以最初当我
yeah so originally when i
开始组建团队时
started the team
我们有意让整个
we intentionally made the whole
类似于视图团队的工作方式。
similar to how the view team works we
让它在结构上相当
make it quite
在结构上很松散
loose in terms of structure
团队成员只是决定
team members just decide
什么是重要的
what's important
足够让他们在游戏中投入时间的工作
enough for them to work on to invest their time game
所以没有真正的
so there's no really
严格的责任本身
hard responsibilities per se
基本上，我没有，我没有到处去说嘿
essentially i don't i don't go around and say hey
就像这是你的工作
like this is your job
你需要做这个
you need to do this
或类似的东西
or anything like that
而其中一个原因是
and one of the reasons
人们成为团队成员的原因之一
people become team members similar
我试图在开放源码周围做的事情是
to how i try to do things around open source is
积极的贡献者
motivated contributors
通常会出现在
typically will show up the
自己站出来
step up by themselves
因为他们通常对这个项目充满热情
because they are generally passionate about the project
所以
so
他们有自然的动力去注意什么是重要的
they have the natural drive to notice what's important
因为他们在思考如何改进项目
because they are thinking about how to improve the project
所以他们注意到需要解决的问题
so they notice the problems that needs to be solved
他们会努力去做
and they work on it
我认为这对于
and i think that's critical in
我认为这对建立一个能够自我驱动的团队至关重要
building a team that can be self driven
在某种程度上
in a way
因此，除此之外，我们试图通过每周的分流会议来做
so outside ofthat we try to do by weekly triage meetings where
所以
so
我们试图在我们不开会的时候，把问题分门别类地组织起来
we try to organize in triage that issues when we're not meeting
把它们分为不同的优先类别
put them into different priority categories
当一个问题进来的时候
when an issue comes in
我们看到好吧，这是一个功能请求还是一个降压报告
we see okay is this a feature request or a buck report
所以这些都是有法可依的，我们有一个工作流程。
so these are kind of codified we have a workflow for that
因此，团队中的每个人都可以帮助
so everyone anyone on the team can help
把问题放到正确的桶里
to put the issues in the right buckets
所以我们有一个板块
so we have a board
我们有一个板子，所有这些问题都被分类
where all these issues are kind of sorted
分成不同的类别
into different categories
所以在我们的团队会议上
so during our team meetings is where
我们大多数人都会聚在一起，按照优先级来处理这些问题
most of us would get together and go through these by priority
和
and
通常，如果一个问题是没有争议的
usually if if a issue is non controversial
团队成员就可以提出解决方案。
team members can just whoever happens to work on
就可以提出一个解决方案，如果
it can just propose a solution and if
另一个团队成员证明了这一点
another team member proves it
我们就可以直接合并，然后去做
we can just merge and go right
所以通常
so typically
我们讨论的事情和会议是那些
the things we discuss and meetings are the ones that
有相对较大的影响
have relatively bigger impact
我们是否需要达成共识或直接从我这里获得投入？
do we need to get a consensus or get input from me directly
来决定我们的行动说好吧，这是我们要做的事情
to call our shots say okay this is what we're gonna do
这不是我们要做的事情
this is not what we're gonna do
所以我认为到目前为止，这对我们来说是非常有效的
so i think so far that's been working pretty well for us
而且很明显
and obviously
这一切都很有效
all of this kind of works
因为有马蒂亚斯，他不知疲倦地
because there's matias who's just tirelessly
他不知疲倦地与团队以外的人接触
sort of reaching out to people outside the team
并带来反馈
and bringing feedback
所以
so
他可以为我们提供内部信息，让我们做出更明智的决定。
he can provide the inside for us to make more informed positions
所以，是的，这几乎是它的工作方式。
so yeah that's pretty much how it works
我还想补充一点
i would also like to add
所以是的，我真的很高兴我发生Evan是如何
so yeah i'm really happily i occur how evan is
构建这个团队和
structuring this team and
帕塔格领导的会议等等。
patag is leading the meetings and so on and
在其中一次
in one of the
在一次会议上，好像是半年前
meetings likethink half a year ago also
我需要打一针或者给Anthony Fu，因为
i need to make a shot or to anthony fu because
我们讨论了我认为是关于
we had a discussion about i think about just
这就是我们使用的测试系统。
and that's the test system we are using invited save
是真的很慢
is really slow
是的，然后我们做了我认为是一个笑话，我们说
and yeah then we made i think it came off of a joke that we said
像我们测试，然后
something like we test and then
第二天的食物
and food on the next day
创建了测试，并围绕它建立了一个完整的生态系统
created the test and around that is a complete ecosystem
老板的子弹等等，安东尼也在
boss bullet and so on and anthony is also
推广最近的积极项目
pushing out the positive recent projects
像其他人一样，而且
like no one elseand
我依靠他在我的Oatma酱项目中，我正在
i'm depending on him on in my oatma sauce project i'm
依靠我的公司项目
depending on my company projects
因此，即使是你也不例外
and so not also even you
视图生态系统，但也包括安东尼。
the view ecosystem but also anthony this
都有存储库
all have has repositories
是的，它是一个巨大的生态系统。
it's so it's yeah it's such a huge ecosystem
而且
and
在过去的一半时间里，我没有在这里做任何这么多的事情。
in the last half here i didn't do any so much in
杂草了，和以前一样，因为
weed anymore and as before because
因为我成为了faker jazz的维护者。
because i became the maintainer of faker jazz
和但是
and but
甚至这也有帮助，因为
even this is helping because
当我使用像v和view以及v test之类的东西时
when i'm using stuff like v and view and v test and so on
我可以向Patak报告
i can report back
向Patak报告我们是如何使用这些东西的，而且
stuff to patak how we use that and
还有
also
我们
we
我们还讨论了
discussed
一个关于劳动的例子和
an example about labours and
git up如何管理
git up how to manage
储存库等等。
repository and so on and
所有这些项目
all these projects
互相改进
improve
彼此的关系
by each other
是的，这也是非常非常酷的
yeah and that's also really really cool
是的
yeah
谢谢你，其实我觉得
thank you and i actually i feel
其实我觉得自己的功劳太大了
quite being over over credit
所以我想和维塔斯类似 我认为维塔斯不是一个人的作品
so i guess similar to vit i think vitas is not a one man work
那就像...
and that's like um
我想这是为社会创造的。
i think that's created to the community and
我们有的东西或者说我们为海滩建立的基础
the thing we had or the foundation we had for the beach
所以第一个想法
so the the first idea
我们的团队提出的第一个要求是
or the first demand that comes from our team to
说什么什么测试地狱
say what what the test inferno
我们会建议和
we would recommend and
核心的镁元素，就像嗯，这是
the core magnesian to like um that's
维生素流淌的未知是
vit runny unknown is
基于维生素提供的功能和最初的想法
based on the feature vit provide and also the initial idea
我们的工作是解决Preya提供的SSR问题。
we work sound knocks to solve the ssr issues that preya provide
所有这些都是为了使维塔斯成为一个可能的想法
to all these things to make vitas possible as an idea
然后我们
and then we
然后我们在Patak和许多人的帮助下组建了一个Vitas团队。
have a kind of vitas team with the help of
在Patak和许多
from patak and from many
我们的团队成员的帮助下，使这些事情发生，委员会
our team members to make these things happens and the committee
他们推动了这些工具的发展
they kind of push the tools forward
以达到我们目前的状态
to be the current states that we
某种程度上是非常
kind of being like very
满足的方式，能够
satisfy ways to being able to
适应我们的需求与像更多
fit our needs with the like more
与适合的生态系统合作
collaborations with the fit ecosystem
我认为这就是我所做的事情
and i think that's being just being what i am
其中一个例子，我们如何
one of the examples that how we
团结这个
united this
社区和
community and
我想，这就是我们如何将这个社区联合起来并使之成为一个普遍性的社区。
make things i think universals for each others
我也想把它关闭
i would also like to shut out
就像我们给每个人都打了预防针
like since we are giving shutouts to everybody
给雅恩和萨菲，就像萨菲也会在这里一样
to yarn and to safi that is like safi shall be here also
就像Hin normalis在会议上在团队会议上一样
that like hin normalis in the meetings in the team meetings
而且他们一直在做
and like they have been doing
他们在Triashin和修复盒子方面做了如此惊人的工作
such an amazing work with triashin and fixing box
就像在过去
like in the past
六个月或一年的时间里，像
six months or a year like
如果你把Chassim考虑进去，在第三位发生了什么？
if you take chassim to account what happened in bit three
就像我们有八个
like we had eight
八百个问题开放
eight hundred issues open
和像他们开始的春天
and like they started the spring
关闭它的时候，yarn发了一条微博说
to close it yarn send a tweet saying
我将
i will
把开放的问题减少到我不知道像什么
take the open issues down to i don't know like what
一百期，我不知道什么时候
one hundred i don't know whenever
有一天你会达到
you are going to reach someday
但它从八百个变成了四百个
but it went from eight hundred to four hundred
两个月的时间里，那是
shass in like two months and that was
就像沙士一样令人印象深刻
like shads just impressive
就像苏达也参与到了其中一样
like also soda got involved there would like
这就像一个人的领导
which like the lead of a one
去通过所有的问题
to go through all of the issues
而这就像我是惊人的像去像每一个每一个
and that just like i'm amazing like going like every every
单一问题和信用像一个精神
single issue and credit like a mental
它不像我被称为它，但像一个地图
and it's not like that i was called it but like a map
的类别是什么，我们应该关注的事情
of categories of what are the things that we should focus on
与月球前进，这也是非常有用的
with moon forward that is also really helpful
这是非常鼓舞人心的，因为我刚刚给了这个讲座关于
this is so inspiring because i just gave this talk about
如何为开放源码做贡献
how to contribute to open source
今天我正在谈论这一切，并且
and was talking about all this today and
我想你知道像
i think you know like
你刚才提到的一些东西，Mateus是很好的方法，其他的人有可能参与进来。
some of the stuff you just mentioned mateus are great ways that
其他人有可能参与进来，你知道
other people could potentially get involved you know
你不需要考虑
you don't have to think about
我不是
i'm not
你不必考虑我没有安东尼那么好，也不必创造所有这些东西
never as good as anthony and creating all these things
但你知道还有很多其他的方式可以让你成为
but you know there's so many other ways you can become
所以
so
对开放源码项目的成功至关重要，比如Beat。
critical to the success of open source projects such as beat so
我想还有人要讲
i think somebody else was going to talk
但我听到
though did i hear
有人取消了静音，想做其他评论
somebody unmute and want to make other comments
我只想说谢谢你
i'll just try and say thank you
在这一点上
at that point
这个房间里有这么多的爱
there's so much love in this room
不，这真的很好，还有
no it's really great and also
我还得说，你知道的，你知道的，你知道的。
i have to say you know cutus and shout out to
听见你的方式
kind of hearing the way
Evan你决定用你们两个人的方式来组织团队
evan you kind of decided to structure the team with both of you
和节拍
and beat
你知道这很惊人
you know it's amazing what
惊人的是，现金和它的人谁走到一起
cash and it people who come together
想解决困难问题的人，在没有政治的情况下可以做到这一点。
who want to solve hard problems can do with lack of politics
所以
so
很高兴看到能够发生的创新
it's great to see the innovation that has been able to happen
你知道有点像在企业门外
you know kind of like outside corporate doors
如果我可以这么说的话，在企业的开放源码之外
outside of corporate open source if i could say that
所以我想你知道那种去，你知道你们都有
so i guess you know kind of going to that you know you all have
提供了很多非常了不起的例子，说明
provided a lot of really amazing examples on how
这里的团队成员
team members here
有你知道能够帮助
haveyou know been able to help
成功的例子
vet be successful
但其他人如何能参与其中呢？
but how can others get involved you know
对于坐在那里听着的开发者来说，现在想要
for that developer sitting there listening right now wanting to
想做下一件事，比如他们能做什么来帮助兽医？
wanting to do the next thing like what can they do to help vet
好吧，我认为
well i think
有不同的方式
there are different ways of
成为社区的一部分并作出贡献
being part of the community and contributing
所以
so
我总是说，即使只是
i always say even just
上网聊天，互相帮助
going on discord and help each other out
回答别人的问题
answering other people's questions
也是一种贡献
is a form of contribution
所以分享知识分享经验
so share a knowledge share experience
回答问题，也许我也会堆叠溢出，所以这些都是
answering questions maybe i'll stack overflow also so these are
任何人都可以做的最低限度的事情
the lowest kind of hanging fruits anyone can do
如果你想走得更远
if you want to go a bit
贡献自己的力量
further and directly contribute to v yourself
你可以看一下我们的期刊列表
you can take a look at our issue list
我们总是有大量的新问题涌入
we always have tons of new issues coming in
所以帮助我们分流它们
so help us triage them
你知道，如果这样的话，通常
you know if so typically
我们花了很多时间来解决这个问题。
we try it we spend a lot of time figuring out with
如何重现一个问题，所以帮助我们
how to reproduce a problem so help us
你知道你可以帮助我们
you know you can help us with
证实好吧，这也发生在我的系统上
verifying okay this is happening on my system as well
这是发生的，你知道
this is happening you know
也许可以减少再现的范围，使之更容易
maybe reducing the scope of the reproduction to make it easier
让我们更容易确定问题所在
for us to identify the problem
或者即使你自己发现了这个问题
or even if you identify the fix yourself
你知道的，提交一份报告来修复它
you know submit a pr to fix it
所以
so
这些都是一种自然的进步，对吗？
these are kind of natural progression right
所以你可以从帮助别人开始
so you can start with just helping other people out
然后帮助三根问题
and then helping trirogen issues
一旦你做了一段时间，你就会对它有所了解。
and once you do that for a while you kind of get a hand of it
你也可以
you can also
跟随阿拉娜的问题，看看它是如何被解决的
follow alana issue to see how it got fixed
跟踪整个过程
to follow through the process
看看其他人是如何提交报告的
see how other people have submitted a pr
所以你可以从中学习，然后你就可以自己做了。
so you learn from it and then you can do it yourself
我认为这不仅仅适用于V
i think this kind of applies not just to v
也适用于任何类型的开源项目，对吗？
but to any kind of open source project right
所以
so
如果你不知道如何进入，你就必须学习
if you don't know how to get in you kind of have to learn
你就得学习一下
around a little bit
看看别人是怎么做的
just see how other people are doing it
这就是我进入开源项目的原因
that's how i got into open source
这也是我学习写代码的原因
that's how i learned to write code actually
我是通过阅读github上其他人的代码来学习的
i learned by just reading other people's code on github
因为一切
because everything
是开放的，所以
is open right so
所有求爱者所做的事情也都是开放的
all the things that courting numbers are doing are also open
对，你可以
right you can
你可以看看你知道的人们提交的PSR，以吃
take a look at you know the prs people have submitted to eat
看看他们是如何使用它的
see how they're working with it
这也有助于你熟悉代码库。
that helps you familiarize with the code base as well
所以是的
so yeah
事实上，很多人都是这样开始的
that's in fact how a lot of people got
我们大部分的核心团队成员都是通过提交小的PRS开始的
most of our core team members started by submitting small prs
你知道，mythia提交的第一个项目
you know the first pr
mythia提交的第一个项目只是修改了一个标题
mythia submitted was just fixing a title
然后他就越来越多地参与进来
and then he got more and more involved
并最终成为团队成员。
and eventually become a team member right
所以
so
你从小事做起，坚持做下去，我们就会
you start with small things do it consistently and we will
你知道那些与项目互动的团队成员
you know the team members who interact with the project
每天都会注意到，你一直在那里
daily will notice that you've been there
你一直在贡献，所以
you've been contributing so
所以我们有一个提名过程，在这个过程中
so we have a nomination process where
团队的现有成员可以说，嘿
team current team members can say hey
这个人最近
this person has been
最近做了很好的工作，我们认为
doing great work lately and we think
他或她应该加入我们的团队。
he or she should be on the team and
我们会这样做，所以
we'll do that so
这就是典型的过程，在这个过程之外，如果你对v本身的工作不感兴趣的话
that's the typical process and outside of it if you're
如果你对v本身的工作不直接感兴趣
not directly interesting working on v itself
你可以创造出拔苗助长，对吗？
you can create pluckings right
所以，因为事实上
so because in fact
很多人们想要解决的问题
a lot of problems that people are trying to solve
可能不适合在VED核心里面解决，因为
may not be suitable to be solved inside ved core because
我们确实有一个
we do have a
范围问题，因为
scope problem where
因为VID在整个网络工具领域有太多的接触
because vid has so much exposure to the whole
网络工具场景，对吗？
web tooling scene now right
有时我们有一种倾向，说好的
sometimes we have a tendency of saying okay
我们希望Feed能做到这一点
we wish feed could do this
但也许这样做并不是最好的主意，因为这是有可能的
but maybe it's not the best idea to do it because it's possible
因为它可以通过构建或插入来实现
by just building or plugging for it
在这种情况下
in that case
你可以用一个插件来解决你自己的问题，发布它
you can solve your own problem with a plugging publish it
这样其他人就可以重复使用你的工作
so that other people can reuse your work
我认为这也是一个很好的方法
i think that's also a great way
对生态系统的贡献
of contributing to the ecosystem
有一件事
one thing that
补充一下Evans所说的
adding up what evans said
在杂草中，特别是像
in weed in particular like
贡献的质量，比如问题，比如
the quality of contributions like issues like
问题的报告方式
how the issues are reported
和PRS像他们中的大多数
and the prs like most of them
是来自于
are coming from
其他项目的维护者，因为像
the maintainers of the other projects because like
如果它也增长了很多
if it also grows a lot
伴随着所有其他项目的参与
with all the other projects that are involved
所以大家说的这个事情，就像
so this thing that everyone say about like
去杂草丛生的地方，看看其他人是如何做PRS的
go to weed and check how others are like doing the prs
或者他们是如何甚至
or how they are even
一个结构在
a structure in
他们的想法，不喜欢他们是如何在问题的百分比
their thoughts no like how they are percent in the problem
这是一个学习的好地方，因为
it is a great place to learn that because
你将会看到一个来自
you're going to see a pr from
富有的人从雷亚姆那里进行
rich carries from rayam from
像从快速的人从
like the people from quick from
像丹尼尔-罗伊，来自诺克斯，像他们一样，他们都是伟大的
like daniel roy from knox like they like they are all great
开源狐狸，所以你会学到很多东西
open source fox so you're going to learn a lot
跟随他们，就像天堂一样疯狂
by following them like heaven is insane
没错，是的
exactly yeah
所以我认为
so i think
我看到很多初学者或刚开始接触开源的人的情况是
what i see a lot from beginners or newcomers to open source is
首先，你不知道
first of all you don't know
从哪里开始
where to start
第二
and the second
有时，也许你第一次尝试提交一份报告。
is sometimes maybe you try for the first time you submit a pr
但
but
有一些小东西，这是一种常见的
there are little things that's kind of common
礼仪开放源码的地方
etiquetteopen source where
比如当你提交一份报告时
like when you submit a pr
有一些事情你应该避免，比如不要
there are certain things you should avoid like don't
使用格式化器来格式化
use a formatter to format
整个文件
the whole file
做出不相关的改变，你知道这些小事情
with unrelated changes you know these small things
然后还有
and then also
如何最好地解释你所要解决的问题
how to best explain the problem you're trying to solve
比如如何让它
like how to make it
更加容易
easier
让维护者做出是否合并的决定
for the maintainer to make the decision to whether merge it
事实上，作为一个维护者，我自己
or not in fact as a maintainer myself
很多时候，我最大的纠结是，我得到了一个 "好心人"。
my biggest struggle a lot of times is i get a pr
的意图是好的
with good intentions
但有时可能只是没有真正解释问题
but sometimes maybe it just didn't really explain the problem
足够好，所以我很难
well enough so i was having a hard time
所以我很难理解为什么需要这样做
understanding why this is needed
所以，通常情况下，最好是你知道
so usually it's better to you know
有一个很好的解释，说明要解决的问题是什么
have a good explainer of what problem is trying to solve
我们是如何遇到这个问题的
how we ran into it
为什么这个问题只能在项目核心中解决？
why is why this can only be solved inside the project core
这就是我们试图解决它的方法
and this is how we are trying to solve it
也许你已经解释了其他的解决方案，对吗？
maybe other solutions you've explained right
如果你看一下我们一些框架的PRS
if you look at the prs from
我们的一些框架
some of our framework
合作者
collaborators
在你的基础上构建东西
for building stuff on top of you
通常他们发送的pr是非常高质量的
usually the pr they sent are very high quality
因为他们通常
because they usually
很好地解释了问题
very well explain the problem
他们遇到的问题，并解释
they're running into and explain
为什么他们认为这是正确的解决方案
why they think this is the right solution
这使得我们更容易考虑，比如好的
and that makes it a lot easier for usto consider like okay
这是有意义的，而且
this makes sense and
因此，这也减少了来回奔波的次数。
so it also reduces the amount of back and forth needed
因此，它也减少了来回奔波的次数，所以总体来说
to get feature merch so overall
总的来说，就是让整个过程更快
just makes the whole process faster
所以有一个
so there's a
通过观察别人的工作，肯定能学到很多东西
definitely a lot to learn just by watching other people work
我认为这就是开放源代码的伟大之处
and i think that's the great thing about open source
在github上的好处是
on github is
你知道整个过程都是开放给你学习的
you know all the whole process is open for you to learn
我觉得这真的很了不起
that's really amazing i think
我嘲笑Matia的
i laugh at matia's
因为你知道
little fix because you know
我总是说，我认为每个维护者都是
i always say and i think every single maintainer is
我相信你们团队中的所有人都在想，我们可以从哪里开始？
i'm sure all of you all on the team are like where can we start
也许你可以帮助我们解决 "码头权 "的问题
maybe you could help with the docksright
这是一个我们经常听到的事情
it's a very common thing that we hear
你知道所有的开源项目都需要
that you know all open source projects need and
如果我们看一下，让我们看一个例子
if we look at let's see as an example
现在就像
now right like
那个小项目
that small little pr
把它变成了更惊人的东西，而且
turned it to something so much more amazing and
这就是你知道的
it's you know
这就是小事，不要低估小事和
it's the small things and don't discount the small things and
你的能力是可以参与其中的
your ability to be able to be involved that way
所以我现在很兴奋
so i'm excited now
我需要进入V的生态系统，找出我可以做的事情
i need to go into the v ecosystem and figure out what i can do
你知道我在这场战斗中得到了很大的启发
you know i'm so inspired by this battle
但接下来的问题
but moving on to the next question
JEN要问的是
jen's about to ask like
每个人都在等待的大问题
the big question that everyone's waiting for
是的，那么下一个问题是什么？
yeah so what is next for beat
是的，那是
yeah that's
是的，这是个很重要的问题，说实话
a quite a loaded question and to be honest
说实话，我们并没有打算做这种像
to be honest we don't have this like
说实话，我们并没有打算做那种大乐队的事情，因为
big band kind of thing that we're planning to do because
因为在这个时候，我们认为
at this moment we think
我们已经在本质上达到了
v has essentially reached a
临界质量，有很多更多的
critical mass where there are a lot more
有更多的东西被建立在它的上面
things that's being built on top of it
所以
so
我想这是一个时期，我们正在努力
i think it's a period where we're trying to
稳定下来，让人们在上面进行迭代。
stabilize and let people iterate on top and
因为VED已经经历了它自己的移动
because ved has gone through its own moving
因为VED已经经历了它自己的移动和破坏的阶段，现在
fast and break things phase now
而现在
and now
因为Ved已经经历了它自己的快速发展和破坏阶段，现在其他人正在它上面进行迭代，所以我们不得不
other people are iterating on top of it so we kind of have to
已经开始考虑我们如何确保我们所做的事情
had started thinking about how we make sure that things
我们所做的事情不会影响到在它上面的建设。
we do don't affect things as being a build on top of it
这就是为什么我们也投资于像生态系统这样的东西。
which is why we also invested in things like the ecos ecosystem
ci，它
ci which
确保一切
make sure that everything
我们所做的一切都不会意外地破坏上面的东西。
we land doesn't break things accidentally on top
所以
so
所以我认为现在
so i think right now
就在这个非常时刻，这个重点实际上只是
like for this very moment this focus is in fact just
确保小麦
making sure wheat
能够很好地作为评论层的作用
can serve well as the commentating layer
确保我们
making sure that we
确保你知道
making sure that you know
它是它是因为有
it's it's because there are
还有很多小事情需要我们去解决
still a lot of little things that we need to fix
和
and
我们正试图利用这个机会
we're trying to take this moment to also
收集人们在它上面的反馈，看看
gather feedback from people building on top of it to see
接下来我们可以做什么？
what is the next thing that we can
显著改善他们所有人的情况，因为
significantly improve for all of them because
说实话，从我个人的
to be honest from my personalized
我已经解决了大部分的问题
perspective i've solved most of the problems
我一开始就想用Beat来解决
i started out to solve with beat
作为一个用户，我对它超级满意
like i'm super happy with it as a user myself
但现在
but now
我们有更多的用户，而不仅仅是建立的人
we have more users than just people building
现在，我们有更多的用户，而不仅仅是直接使用V来构建应用程序的人
directly using v to build apps now
我们有这些框架作者
we have these framework authors
而且我们面临着很多不同的需求
and we are facing a lot of different needs
把我们拉向不同的方向
pulling us in different directions
我们需要一个时间来考虑
and we need a time to sort of
思考什么是重叠的东西？
think about what is that overlapping things that
我们可以让所有这些框架一起受益。
we could benefit all of these frameworks together yeah
我想Mattes可能已经有了一些东西，他已经有了
and i think mattes may have something that he's already had
他已经有了自己的想法，他想把他推到前面去
he already has in mind that he wants to push him before
我觉得就像你说的，我们做的很多事情都是这样的
now i think that it's like you said like a lot of what we did
自从有了两个人之后，我们做的很多事情都是在看里面的东西，并试图像
since with two has been like looking inside and trying to like
让它... ...我不知道如何减少盒子的数量
make it i don't know reduce the box like
试图从一些碎布蛋转移到其他金属或
trying to move like from some rag eggs to like other metals or
我知道，我认为向前发展，会有很多的
i know i think that moving forward there will be a lot of
比如说移动到卷起来，不会被
moving to roll up for example that will not be
外界感觉不到那么多
felt that much outside
但在内部，这将使6个更容易维护
but internally it will make six more maintainable
我们可以替换一些部件，比如
we could replace some parts maybe like
代替pos css
instead of pos css
我们可以使用包裹团队的照明CSS。
we could use lighting css from the parcel team
有一个来自Devon的Pock在那里转悠
there was a pock going around there from devon
所以是的，我不知道我怎么想的
so yeah i don't know like i think
一段时间内，它仍然是一种更多的内省
for a while it will still be kind of like more introspective
变化和提供基础
changes and giving the base that
你说的是需要别人来创新的 是的
you say is needed for others to innovate on yeah
有一件事我们一直在
one thing we've been
我们一直在考虑一个潜在的事情，但这是
one potential thing we've been thinking about but this is
我们一直在考虑一个潜在的问题，但这是更进一步的问题
a bit more further down the road
我们最终想解决的一个瓶颈是
one of the bottleneck that we want to solve eventually
从长远来看是
in the long term is the
开发过程中的请求量
the amount of requests during development
当你有成千上万的请求时
when you have like thousands of requests
他们只是在网络层面上的拥挤
they're just congesting at the network level
这一点，v to self是无法解决的
which v to self is not able to solve
只是由于急切的性质与
just due to the eager nature vs
本机的ESM导入，但可能有潜在的
native esm imports but there could be potential
的方法来解决这个问题，例如
ways to work around it for example
用潮湿的捆绑物
with wet bundles
但这些都是非常早期的规格，而且是大量涌入的规格
but these are kind of specs that are really early and influx
但我们最近已经开始
but we've recently started
我们最近开始与浏览器的人接触，他们是直接在浏览器上工作的人。
got in contact with the browser folks who's
我们最近开始与直接在浏览器上工作的人接触，我们正试图
directly working on the browsers and we're trying to
交换意见，看看未来浏览器的哪些功能
exchange notes and see what future features in
浏览器中的哪些功能可以使我们受益
the browser could definishly benefit
我们可以利用这些功能来
feat that we could leverage to
改进
improve
另一件事是
and the other thing is
是啊是啊，所以我们最近一直在做相当多的
yeah yeah so so we've been recently doing quite a bit of
与从事浏览器工作的人进行沟通，以了解
communication with people working on browsers to see where
有什么潜在的方法可以解决这个问题？
what are the potential ways to address the spot on act
我想这可能是我最想解决的事情之一。
i think that is probably one of the things i
我想这可能是我最想解决的问题之一，但在短期内
i want to solve them most but in the short term
但在短期内，这是很困难的，所以我们有点儿
it's quite difficult so we're kind of
所以我们把希望寄托在浏览器的未来规格上
setting our hopes on future specs in the browser
所以我们把希望寄托在浏览器的未来规格上，希望能直接帮助我们解决这个问题
directly that maybe can help us with that
你们其他人呢？
what about the rest of y'all any
任何希望和未来
any hopes and futures
你们有什么希望吗？
that you're all are hoping for
我想，对不起
i think sorry
你可以继续下去
you can go ahead so down
好的
okay
所以我认为它的主要特点是快速和精简，所以
so i think the main characteristics of it is fast and lean so
我认为胜利会在这两方面走得更极端
i think victory will go more extreme on these two sides
例如，在胜利中，我们削减的
for example in victory we cut the
发表的大小在三分之一
published size in a third
和实际上与卷起三
and actually with the roll up three
发布，而在这个四
release and in this four
我们可以进一步削减安装尺寸，因为
we can further cut the install size because
Roll up将他们的浏览器绑定从mpm包中移除，而
roll up removed their browser bond from the mpm package and
另一方面
on the other
另一方面，Beat是非常简单的，所以嗯
hand beat is very simple so um
现在，当我们更多地关注我们内部的
now as we looking more inside our
内部复杂的城市，所以
internal complex city so
许多新的选项将被放入实验性标志中，并且
many of the new options will go into the experimental flag and
这将保持新的功能
that will keep the new features
更容易开始，而且
easier to start with and
我们可能会找到一种方法，将其整合到现有的选项中去
we might find a way to integrate it into the existing options
而不会让新用户感到困惑
without confusing new users
而这正是我所期待的
and that's what i was looking forward
是的，我认为你对我来说，主要是冲上去的。
yeah i think your mostly for me is punching up
所以一切都会保持不变，但会更好
so everything will stay the same but better
比如说像rollock free
so like rollock free for example
我们内部有变化，但你会有一些变化。
we change internally but you would a few it
这将是一个透明的变化
it would be a transparent change
有一些改进，从预先捆绑，我们
and there's some improvements from pre bundling that we
我想我们希望从
i guess we want to bring back from
早期的V树阿尔法时代
the early v tree alpha days
Maya的变化不应该影响你，它应该只是工作。
maya always change shouldn't affect you it should just work
神奇地
magically
所以你会得到盒装后的性能，你不需要
so you'll get the performance after box you don't have to
乱七八糟的冲突或什么的
mess around conflicts or anything
所以我想是的，到目前为止有一种未来的V。
so i guess yeah there's kind of future v so far
是的
yeah
是啊，我有点同意，而且
yeah i kind i kinda agreed and
对于我这样的人
for my kind person
个人的观点，我觉得
personal perspective i feel that
作为委员会，我们已经有了这个生态系统
as the committee we already have the ecosystem
我们已经有了那种
we already have that kind of
被批准，一个节拍本身是非常灵活的
being approved that a beat itself is being very flexible
既然我们有这么多的工具在上面，而且
and since there we have so many tools on top of it and
我觉得禁忌本身我们应该有点限制我们的范围，以
i think forbid itself we should kind limit our scope to
不引入那种真正的像
not introducing that really like
像新的功能，但我们
like new features but we
现在可以像把创新留给前面的工作，我们
could now like leave the innovations to the front work and we
我们不能已经看到，我们得到了很多新的
we can't already see that we got a lot of new
我们有一个朋友
we got a friend
我们得到了朋友的作品
we got the friend works
有很多新功能和新想法的大拇指
with a lot thumbs of new features and new ideas
而且已经在这个谈话中进行了，所以
and already going on in this talk and so
可以感觉到，对于维生素本身，我们应该继续做我们的
can feel that for vit itself we should keep doing our
工作，以像优化和使事情更快，或像
jobs to like optimize and to make things even faster or like
改进事情本身，所以
improve the things itself so
我不觉得我们不会有像
i can't feel that we won't have like
那周要展示的主题演讲
keynote to showcase that week
我们不能有一大堆的新功能出现
we can't have a ton of new features coming in that
让人兴奋
get people excited
但我认为我内心的工作是保持事情
but i think the works inside of me to keep things
稳定，并保持事物的可维护性和快速性是
stable and to keep things like very maintainable and fast is
仍然是一项重要的工作，以
still a crucial job to
使它
make it
让整个社区都能
for the whole community to
使用一个东西
use a thing
哦
oh
这是有道理的，虽然
that makes sense although
我知道每个人在你说话的时候
i know everybody whenever you talk
ANTHONY都在等待测试，以弄清楚
anthony is waiting on beta breath to figure out
你被告知你接下来要创建什么图书馆，所以
what library are told you're gonna create next so
我们很兴奋
we're excited
我觉得任何想看这个的人都应该
i feel like anybody who wants to see that we gotta just
继续关注你的github
keep watching your github
但你知道我喜欢这个 我是说我听到的关于V的事情
but you know i love that i mean the things that i hear
关于V和那种你们如何稳定和
about v and kind of how you all are stabilizing and
试图让它变得可维护，并且
trying to make it maintainable and
不做破坏性修改或很少做破坏性修改
no breaking changes or very little breaking changes
这些都是非常了不起的目标，我
are really amazing goals and i
你知道，我觉得这也是视图所做的，所以令人惊讶的是
you know i feel like that's also what view has done so surprise
令人惊讶的是，非常相似的团队在做同样的事情
surprise very similar team working on the same thing
但伊万，我知道你知道这些年来，你知道
but evan i know you know over the years you know
每当我和你谈起观点
whenever i talk to you about view
它总是像
it's always like
只是提高性能和改善事情，而且
just improving performance and improving things and
你知道的，就是不断地改进引擎盖下的东西
you know constantly like improving things under the hood
所以我很高兴听到
so it's great to hear
嗯，有点像一样的
um kind of like the same
我首先有一个经验
i have first an experience on
只是一个项目要经历不同的阶段
just a project going through different phases
因为当你
because when you're
刚开始的时候，你可以
just starting out you can
做任何你想做的事情，然后当你只有早期采用者的时候
do whatever you want then when you have only early adopters
你就可以把大的变化、大的改进
you can ship big changes big improvements
而不太在意
with while caring less about
破坏建立在它上面的东西，因为早期采用者
disrupting things built on top of it because early adopters
通常是
are typically
因为早期采用者通常对这种事情更加开放，但是
more open to that kind of thing but
当你达到一个临界质量时，你有很多的
when you reach a critical mass you have a lot of
你有更多的观众
you have a wider audience
你有一些人
you have people
他们只是在生产中使用你的东西来建造东西
who are just using your thing to build stuff in production
和
and
有一大群用户，他们
there are big group of users who
对他们来说，首要任务是
for them first
稳定性是他们的首要任务，他们不希望事情突然中断。
priority is stability they don't want things to suddenly break
而在某一时刻
and there will be a point where
你解决了这个问题
you are solving the problem
足够好的时候，稳定性在某种程度上成为
well enough that stability in a way becomes
一个真正重要的价值
a really important value
的重要价值
for the thing to uphold
所以我认为壮举是在一个
so i think feat is in a
过渡时期
transition period where
我们想从本质上把我们的焦点带回来一点儿
we want to essentially bring back our focus a little bit
而不是考虑好
instead of thinking about okay
下一件大事是什么 下一个新事物是什么
what's the next big thing what's the next new thing
我们会说好吧
we're going to say okay
如何使目前的事情变得更好
how to make the current things better
如何让它保持同样的工作方式，但更快更精简
how to keep it working the same way but faster leaner
更强壮，更稳定的引擎。
and more robust and more stable under the hood
我认为
i think
这将是重点，至少现在是这样的
that would be the focus for at least for now
非常感谢您
thank you so much
我们的时间快到了
and we are just about out of time
但最后一个问题，是否会有另一个Vitcomf？
but one last question will there be another vitcomf
我不知道
i don't know
你喜欢这一次吗？
do you enjoy this one
肯定的
sure
我听说下一个是V测试冲突
i heard the next one as v test conflict
哦
oh
等等，等等，我们
wait wait we
一年做一次
do one one year
维塔斯来了一年，一年的维塔斯会议
vitas come one year one year vid conf
我想是的
i think yeah
是的，去吧，去吧
yeah go go go
是的，我想
yeah i think
我想在十分钟内
in guys like in ten minutes
我们又重新开始了，而且还会有另一个
we were starting over again and there would be another
是的
yeah
哈
哈哈哈
好了，请大家继续关注
well stay tuned everyone
谢谢大家参加这个讨论会
thank you all for joining this panel
感谢大家参加veecomp
thank you everyone for joining veecomp
今天的会议真是太精彩了
today it was absolutely amazing
如果你还没有回去，或者你错过了一些讲座
if you haven't gone back and or if you miss some of the talks
我的意思是有一些非常惊人的公告
i mean there has just been some really amazing announcements
最近，你知道故事书中的Dino
lately you know storybook dino
你知道故事书中的恐龙和其他许多人都发表了一些非常重要的声明
both made some really big announcements as well as many others
所以我们会在下一次见到你
so we will see you next time
感谢大家的加入
thank you all for joining
也非常感谢你的团队
and thank you so much for your team for
感谢你们的团队今天来到这里，并且在你们的时区这么早起床
being here today and being up
在你们的时区这么早，非常感谢你们
so early on your time zones thank you so much
谢谢你，再见
thank you bye
谢谢你
thank you
谢谢你，再见
thank you bye bye
帮助
help
下面再给大家介绍一下
below again everyone
我们做到了第一个12小时的结束
we made it to the end of the first 12
那些小组讨论不是很好吗？
hours weren't those panels so good
但整个会议是不是真的很精彩？
but wasn't really just the whole conference so amazing
这是很好的做法
this was so well done
大家给马太斯鼓鼓掌吧
everybody give a round of applause to mattaius
和所有在幕后工作的了不起的人
and all of the amazing folks that were behind the scenes
并把它放在一起
and that put this together
他们只是做了这样一个令人难以置信的工作
they've just done such an incredible job
无论你是
and whether you are
刚刚起床
just getting up
还是像我一样要去睡觉，这里已经很晚了
or maybe heading to bed like me it is very late here
继续在微博上发帖，让我们知道你最喜欢的讲座
keep posting on twitter let us know your favorite talks
你可以用vitcomp或
you can use at vitcomp or
标签vitcomph
hashtag vitcomph on
twitter，让我们知道你喜欢什么
twitter and let us just know what you liked
你喜欢什么
what you enjoyed
我们有
and we had
我们和你们在一起非常开心，这一切都将重新开始。
so much fun being with you and this is all going to start again
马特奥应该马上就到了
mateo should be in here in just a second
他显然刚从小组中出来
he obviously just got off the panel
但他将会加入我的行列
but is going to be coming in and joining me
但只要继续发帖，让大家知道
but just keep posting and letting
大家都知道你想和我们一起回到这里
everybody know that you want to be back here with us
明年再来
again next year
并展示所有这些支持
and showing all of this support
我很高兴看到所有这些惊人的工具
i was so excited to see all of these amazing tools
和人们在一起。
and the people that beat really brings together
让这个社区感觉就像一个大家庭 我喜欢我们如何能够
and makes this community feel like a family i love how we can
你没有任何框架战争，只是我们所有的人
doesn't you don't have any framework wars it's just all of us
一起享受和参与一切
enjoying and being a part of everything together
我喜欢这个会议给我们带来的东西
and i loved what this conference did to us
我喜欢这次会议对我们社区的影响，看到大家在
the community and seeing everybody in
聊天时看到大家都很开心
the chat was just so amazing
我知道Patrick Armantea
i know patrick armantea
我知道Patrick Armantea花了很多时间，比如说做discord
spent a lot of time like doing the discord
把所有的表格都设置好，就像一个时间表一样
having all of the forms set up that was like a schedule
一切都想得很周到，做得很好
everything was just so well thought out and done so well
我们希望每个人都喜欢它，并且
and we hope everyone enjoyed it and
没有看到很多的问题
didn't see a lot of issues
但感谢所有的版主，他们在外面帮助保持
but thank you to all the moderators that were out
感谢所有在现场帮助保持
there helping keep
感谢所有在那里帮助保持聊天清洁的版主，感谢大家对我的帮助。
chat clean and thank you everyone for being kind to
我是说
i mean did
每个人都有机会检查所有的小组，我知道
everybody get a chance to check out all the panels i know
我们有一个框架小组
we had a framework panel
我们有刚刚发生的 "脚 "小组
we had the feet panel that just happened
然后今天早些时候有一个小组
and then there was a panel earlier today
那是非常激动人心的，还有12个小时
that was very exciting twelve more hours
再过十二个小时
twelve more hours
我知道人们正在改变，还有12个小时
i know people are changing twelve more hours
所以我们还有12个小时要走
so we have twelve more hours to go
这有点疯狂和
it's kind of crazy and
激动人心的是，所有这一切都将在原地重新开始。
exciting that all of this is going to start over again in place
所以如果你刚起床
so if you're just getting up
你没有错过加入聊天，实际上
you haven't missed outjoin in the chat and actually
我想在这之后会有一个讨论的阶段
i think there's going to be a discord stage of it
在那之后，不幸的是
after that unfortunately
我得去睡觉了
i have to go to bed
所以我不会加入的
so i won't be joining that
但如果你有兴趣的话，请加入beatland的对话。
but if you're interested get in the beatland discord
我想我们有一个东西，我们可以把它放在下面。
i think we have a thing that we can put below for the
链接来加入
link to join
我不记得那是什么了，我什么都不会。
don't remember what it is i'm failing on everything
我以为Mateos现在已经在这里了
and i thought mateos would be in here by now
但现在我们在这里，我只是在吐槽，所以
but here we are i'm just spitballing now so
我希望每个人都有一个惊人的时间，我们走吧
i hope everyone had an amazing time there we go
我想我们现在有他了
i think we have him now
但你是静音的
you're muted though
他就在那里
there he is
我在这里
i'm here
好的，嘿
okay hey
情况如何
how's it going
我很好，我很好，我们是现场直播吗？
i'm fine i'm fine are we live right
我不知道我们是否活着
i don't know if we are live
我想是的
i think right
哇，是的，没错
wow yeah right
看一看我3盘你
看看看我3盘you
这真是太棒了
it was amazing
我刚刚花了几分钟的时间
i just spent like the last couple of minutes
就告诉大家做得多好
just telling everybody how well done
这次会议
this conference
为你点赞 为所有幕后团队点赞
was and kudos to you kudos to all the team behind the scenes
主持人
the moderators
让这一天变得精彩的人们
the people that just made this an amazing day
是的
yeah
它的到来是疯狂的
it's coming crazy
我相信你一定很想去
i'm sure you were like going
现在就像现在我们达到了12个小时，这是
it's now like now we are reaching like twelve hours this is
一半的时间，就像永远，每个人都在看
half of it like forever like everybody that is watching
现在留下来，因为
stay now because
就像我们有一个
like we have a
伊万的谈话，我还会再来的，然后是安东尼的谈话
talk from evan a talk like i will be again and then antony
然后卷起我们会在那里
and then roll up we'll be there
所有这些都会再次为你回放
all gonna replay for you again
你会再次得到一整天的时间，所以如果你刚刚起床
you get the whole day again so if you're just getting up
你就不会错过任何东西
you're not missing a thing
是的
yeah
是的，是的，对你们两个说
yeah and yes saying to you two
和所有在现场的版主
and to all the moderators that were there
围绕着这一天
around the day
其实主持工作并没有那么多车，因为
it was not that car actually to moderate because
每个人都像在给别人送花一样
everybody was like sending flowers to each others exactly
我说的是对的
what ii was saying right
当你进来的时候
as you were coming in
我觉得每个人都是那么善良
i was like everyone was so kind
我觉得我们真的不需要很多的节制
i feel like we didn't really need a lot of moderation
这很了不起
which was amazing
但我要感谢所有的版主，这真是不可思议。
but i thank you to all the moderators that was incredible
是的
yeah
是的，很高兴看到
yeah it was really nice to see
很高兴看到白地在一天之内就变成了一个空间
like whitland converted like in one day as a space
所有的社区
where all the communities
就像我刚才说的，在
get together like i was saying there in the
在小麦小组中，现在
in the wheat panel now
我不知道是什么时候开始的固体谈话
that i don't know like when was the solid talk
像所有的固体雾室
like all the solid fog room
来到了这个房间
came to the room
是的
and yeah
我说，这也是像它如何
i said that too is like how it
它是如何把所有这些社区聚集在一起的
beat really brings all of these communities together
感觉就像一个大家庭，我们都很友好
and it felt like a family like we were all being nice
没有框架战争，只是
there were no framework wars it was just
我们所有的人都很善良，都在一起
all of us being kind and being together
这感觉真的很好
which felt really good
是的
yeah
是的是的，正如一些发言人所说，我认为这是
yeah yeah and as some of the speakers said like i think this is
我认为这对共同制度的未来是一件好事。
like this is a good thing for the future of the co system
就像所发生的那样
like what happened like
也像埃文斯说的
also like evans said
现在，像它真的很有趣，看到
now that like isit's really interesting to see
比如说不是每两个星期公布一次
like not like once announcement every two weeks
但像很多人使用它
but like a lot of people use it
这个特殊的日子是一个艰难的日子
this particular day as a hard day
为他们做一个公告
for them to do an announcement
就像来自ESTAGLITZ的人，在工作上有那么多的好处
like from estaglitz that comes in working so much
躺在床上
to actually lounge
冷流在此
cold flow in this
如果你在听第二部分
like if you are listening for the second
如果你听的是第二部分，就像冷流不存在一样，你会了解到它的。
part like cold flow doesn't exist you're going to get to know it
就像没有破坏者一样
like no spoilers
是的，没有，现在没有破坏者
yeah no no spoiler now
但也像一本故事书
but also like a storybook
实际上是在宣布Simpono将发生什么事
actually announcing what is going to happen with simpono
或者像卷轴三Lucas
or like the rollap three lucas
他们就像在选择，他们这个样的像重大的
they're like choosing that they this kind of like significant
不像是
not like is
为拉帕和维塔做的，我想我知道的。
making it for lapa and vita lot closer i think i know
我看到有人在询问股票的情况，哦
i saw people like asking for stock at one point oh
我想，我们刚刚发布了候选作品，你们要放慢脚步。
i'm like we just hit release candidate you guys slow your roll
我们不能让所有东西都在今天发布，对吗？
a little bit we can't have everything released today right
是的，是的，但它也是达到了达到了股票是
yeah yeah but it also was reach reach stock was
难以置信，也像第一部分，当
incredible also like the first part when
他说的是
he was talking about
就像这个比喻说的那样，我们的新结构被打败了
like this analogy of beat us the fresh structure
对生态系统来说，我觉得
like for the ecosystem i seem
我觉得这是很有道理的
like that that's quite on point
听起来真的非常有趣
it was really really interesting to hear
我同意是的
i agree to yeah
我认为所有的演讲都是经过深思熟虑的
i thought all of the talks were just so well thought out
这真的是令人惊奇的一天，而且
it was really an amazing day and
如果你只是来参加的话，你是很难得的。
you were inferior treat if you're just joining in
是啊是啊是啊
yeah yeah yeah
我不知道我们有多少时间，但是...
totally so so yeah i don't know how much time we have like but
你应该
you should
你应该留在这里
like stay around now like
有一件事是很重要的，我想也是要分享的
one thing that is important i think like to share also
现在，像我们做了很多的噪音
now now like we did a lot of noise
当我们开始的时候，很多社区都加入了
when we are started so a lot of communities join
但现在像
but now like
社区的很大一部分人正在加入
a big part of the community is joining
所以如果你邀请他们
so it would be nice if you invite them
来这里
to came here
所以，如果你能分享像Vitcom这样的链接，那就太好了。
so like if you share like the link that is like vitcom
vicon org是睫毛生活
vicon org is lash life
这是一种像他们的链接，你必须分享
that is kind of like their link that you have to share
在那里你将会
there you are going to
就像实际上
like actually
我们将一起解释所有这些
we are going to be together like explaining all these
我知道这只是要重新播放一遍。
i know it's just going to replay over again
是的
yes
所以也许我们现在不应该解释那么多
so maybe we shouldn't explain that much now
但是，是的
but yeah
我们没有设置这个问题 我觉得这很重要
we didn't set there that that i think it's important now
这12个小时的很大一部分不仅是会谈
like a big part of these twelve hours was not only the talks
而且还在这个法庭上一起观看
but was also watching it together in this court
和所有这些类似的渠道，所以我看到像
and in all these like channels so i see like
走出去
go out
邀请其他人，所以你现在得到了同样的经验
invite others and like so you get that same experience now
是的，我
yeah i
完全同意，我
completely agree and i
是的，我完全同意，我向大家提到了
was mentioning to everyone
如果你有一个最喜欢的
that if you have a favorite
谈话或你真正喜欢的东西
talk or something that you really liked about
今天，请确保你在
today make sure you're
在Viet Comp的标签
tagging at viet comp
使用标签 viet comp 并在twitter上分享。
using hashtag viet comp and sharing that on twitter
就像让更多的人加入
like getting more people in
我不相信有两万个注册者
i can't believe twenty thousand registrations
这真是不可思议
it's just incredible
是啊，实际上人们现在还在继续抵制她 是的
yeah and actually the people continue to resist her now yeah
所以我们看到了这个数字，我就像个小鸡一样飞了起来。
so we were seeing the number i was just chicken up and over
是的 是的
yeah yeah
我想应该是23点5分
i think it's like a twenty three point five
现在的注册人数和
k now registrations and
如果我没查错的话
if i check correctly
有像
there were like
一千名新成员加入了Vidland的讨论区
one thousand new members to vidland to the discourt
就像一千名新加入的人
like one thousand new people that join
维德兰，这是
vidland that that's
这是很重要的，因为像其中一个
quite important because like one of the
不让会议
ideas of not making the conference
在一个单独的空间
in a separate space
我们可以说是一个单独的聊天室
let's say like a separate chat
的想法是，让我们使用vidland，所以
was the idea of like let's use vidland so
所有这些运动实际上是和我们在一起的，比如
all this movement actually stays with us like
希望今天在这里工作的一些人
hopefully some of the people that work here today
希望今天在这里工作的一些人能够在这个社区工作，并且留在这里。
like actually like in the community and are going to stay around
然后参与进来，让更多的人
and then like get involved it brings more people
进入你的社区 是的
into your community yeah
我完全同意这一点
i completely agree with that
满足你的社区，他们在哪里，所以现在
and meeting your community where they're at so now
你有所有这些社区成员在那里
that you have like all these community members in there
他们可以找到
they can find
帮助，让他们知道去哪里找这些东西。
help and get they know where to go and look for those things
我知道你提到
i know you mentioned
我知道你曾经提到过，可能会有一个不和谐的阶段
at one point that there might be a discord stage
我不想把你放在
i didn't want to put you on the
我不想把你放在这个位置上
spot
但我提到了关于这个问题 是会发生还是
but i mentioned something about that is that going to happen or
让我们来看看我们的情况如何
let's let's check how we are
在每个人的力量中，都有一个小神志不清的人
in everybody's power a little delirious
是的，在12个小时内，如果我们现在不做的话
yeah in twelve hour more like if we don't do it now
我们可以在一个星期内完成它
we can do it in one week
但是，是的，就像
but but yeah like
之后留下
stay after
就像会议在下半场结束后结束一样
like the conference is over over like after the second half
如果我们在一起，我们决定在这个好时机
and if we are together and we decide at this good moment
就像和社区讨论一样，让我们来做吧
like talk with the community let's do it
好的，听起来不错
okay sounds good
而且也许
and maybe
未来的活动
the ones in the future
你们是否有活动，并将其发布在讨论区？
like do you have events that you post in the discord
人们可以去看看
that people can go and see
就像我知道Vit Comp现在就有这个活动，但是
like i know vit comp has the event in there right now but
你能不能发布一下，比如有什么
would you post like are there
未来的事件或重复发生的事件，Vit Land Discord
future events or reoccurring events that the vit land discord
有
has
这是我第一次参加这样的活动
like this is the first kind of like oh
我们在这个法庭上所做的活动。
ohofficial let's say like event that we did in this court
但是，也许像给像
but maybe like given like the
但鉴于这种反应
reaction that this is having
也许我们应该多做一些
maybe we should do more often like
我知道，比如说在天体的
i know for example like in the astro
不和谐，也许在这个世界上也是
discord and maybe in this world also
你有像每两个星期一次或东西，你得到的
you have like once every two weeks or something that you get
像在一起，只是与社区的人交谈
like together and just talk with the community
所以也许我们应该这样做，比如
so maybe we should do that like
我们应该这样做，比如Asher和Redwood都是这样做的。
asher does that and redwood does that this belt
团队不这样做
team doesn't do it
但我们已经讨论过
but we've talked about
但我们已经讨论过这样做，因为我认为这对于
doing that because i think that's really good for
建立社区参与
building community involvement
特别是在
especially with
这些开放源码的东西，所以
these open source things so
我想这是
i think that is
我认为这对这些社区来说是非常有益的
really beneficial for these communities to have that
因此，这将是非常酷的
so that would be really cool
这其实是个好主意，我觉得
that's actually a good idea i think
我们现在可以讨论
we can discuss now
就像在接下来的12个小时里
like in this next twelve hour
某个时候醒来，讨论这些其他的
wake up sometime to discuss about these other
我还要睡八个小时呢
meta things what i'm gonna sleep for about eight hours
我想我也会这样做的，但是
i think i will do too like but
像蓝色的安东尼汽水
like blue antony soda
像有很多像Evan一样的人
like there's a lot of like evan
有很多人都在拍摄工作，所以
like there's a lot of people that shots work and up so
比如说会有一些主题和版主的交流
like there will be some like exchange of themesand moderators
然后，我们，我们回来了
and then we that we were back
我想就像采取一些
and i wanted to just like take some
时间来再次感谢
time to thanks again like
你将会看到对我们的感谢，但是
you're going to see thanks to us like but
但是，这很好，就像所有这些发生
but it's good like all these happen
也是因为首先像演讲者，像你
also because first like the speakers like you
你说过，这些讲座很精彩，因为
said that like the talks were amazing because
他们真的很像
they really were like
有一些像
there were some that like
就像好莱坞的那种制作
were like hollywood kind of production
就像它只是它只是惊人的所以
like it's just it's just amazing so
谢谢你，非常感谢
thanks thanks a lot
每个人都付出了这么多的努力，有很多人都是第一次做演讲。
everybody that puts so so much effort there were a lot of
有很多第一次做演讲的人，听起来确实非常非常好。
first time as speakers that actually did sound so so so good
我希望他们能去参加其他的会议
i hope they go and have like other conferences
以后还有
later and
是的，谢谢你
yeah like thanks for
建立的
established for
赞助的活动和社区合作伙伴的帮助。
like a sponsoring event and like the community partners also
的帮助和
for the help and
是的，就像感谢
and yeah like thanks
每个人都参与了他们的社区
everybody that was involved their communities
感谢每一个邀请别人的人，并把
thanks everybody that invited others and took
它在这里和
it here and
这也是一种像将被重复作为会议结束的
this is also kind of like going to be repeated as the end
会议的结束，所以
of the conference so
如果你要留下来，就像如果这是
if you're staying like if this is
如果你留在这里，就像在架子上一样，把它当作是
the half and you're staying like shelf like take it as
如果这是你的会议结束了，那么你就会像明天一样观看。
disastain if this is the end of the conference for you
你会在明天看到它
you're watching it like tomorrow
所以是的
so yeah
我不知道，谢谢你的坚持
i don't know and thank you for sticking
谢谢你坚持到最后，在这里和我们在一起
through the whole thing and being here at the end with us
是的，是的，是的
yeah yeah yeah
这是个很好的经验
this has been an amazing experience and
是的，我想我们应该再来一次，你觉得呢？
yeah i think we should repeat it what do you think
我们明年再做一次
we do it again next year
我绝对认为
i absolutely think
我们应该至少在明年再做一次，如果不是在六个月内的话
we should do it at least next year if not in six months
不
no
我只是把这一切
i just put all this
我不知道
i don't know the
皮克斯请拯救我的心
pixier please save my heart
不，不，这不是它
no no it wasn't it
它是它是如此的好
it was it was so good
看到所有这些人走到一起真是太好了
and it's so nice to see all these people come together
我只是喜欢这部分内容
i just love that part of it
是的，是的，是的
yeah yeah yeah
所以是的，我想
so yeah i think
我不会让
i don't let
让我们把它关闭，把战争交给我们两个人吧
let's let's close it and let's give the war to the two of us
是的
yes
把它交给布兰妮和马特罗斯
hand it off to britney and mateos
看到你们了吗？
see you guys do you
非常感谢
thanks a lot